MOUTIALLAH HAMROUNI

SENIOR INDUSTRIAL MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN

CONTACT

+216 29703079

moutiallah.hamrouni@gmail.com

https://moutiea.github.io/portfolio/

3021 Sfax, Tunisia

SKILLS

3D Modeling

Technical plans

Project Management

Documentation and control

Writing reports

Spreadsheet management

Office management

Project planning

Customer and client relations

* * * * * * *



English

Arabic

French



SOFTWARE

• Solidworks

Blender

Microsoft Excel/Word



Analytical Industrial Technician well-versed in installing, maintaining and repairing machinery, equipment and electrical systems while leading teams in troubleshooting electrical and mechanical problems. Experienced in isolating root causes of maintenance problems to develop expedient solutions. Working knowledge of electronic and electrical concepts and operating safety to promote maximum efficiency. Dependable professional with experience providing administrative, organizational and customer service support in virtual environments. Proficient in MS Office and other productivity tools. Possess strong communication and problem-solving skills with time management expertise to consistently meet objectives.

WORK HISTORY

Senior Industrial Maintenance Technician

Société Indusrielle De Grillage "SIG"

09-2020-Current

- Dismantled electrical machinery to replace faulty switches and electrical and mechanical system elements.
- Diagnosed, repaired and replaced faulty electrical, electronic and mechanical components to maintain plant safety.
- Developed, drafted and conducted preventive maintenance procedures to enforce business standards.
- Performed routine preventive maintenance activities and retained copy of equipment programs as backups.
- Quickly responded to internal service calls regarding malfunctioning equipment and completed repairs.
- Performed electrical and mechanical repairs of production equipment to minimize downtime.
- Followed work orders and specifications for machine and equipment replacement, repair, or maintenance.
- Completed daily, weekly, and monthly checklists on building equipment to maintain records of scheduled maintenance procedures.
- Worked with building managers to assess ongoing needs and plan preventive maintenance and cleaning schedules.
- Inspected and maintained equipment to keep items in top working condition.
- Monitored and documented work performance in maintenance logs in compliance with company guidelines.

Production Machine Operator

Flexoprint

06-2023-08-2023

- Calibrated, tested, and adjusted machine settings or controls in preparation for production operations.
- Set up and ran machinery to produce exceptional products for industrial needs.

MOUTIALLAH HAMROUNI

SENIOR INDUSTRIAL MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN

CERTIFICATIONS

- Solidworks Associate Level
- Arduino Level 1&2

INTERESTS

- Developing my everyday skills
- Exploring new technologies
- Content creation

EDUCATION

High school diploma

High School EL Manar, Sfax

2019-2020

Bachelor of Mechanical Engineering

Higher Institute of Industrial Management of Sfax

2020-2023